<resources>

    <!--English-->

    <string name="app_name">SkilEx</string>
    <string name="tag_line">THE ULTIMATE SERVICE APP</string>
    <string name="empty" />
    <string name="error_no_net">No internet access. Please check your connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_occurred">Failed to connect to the server. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="booking_terms">I, agree to the </string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>


    <!--Dialog Fragment-->

    <string name="alert_button_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="alert_button_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="alert_button_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="alert_button_no">No</string>

    <!--User Data-->

    <string name="mobile_number">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="agree">I, agree to the </string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions"> Terms and Conditions </string>
    <string name="skilex_service"> of SkilEx services.</string>
    <string name="referral">Referral Code</string>
    <string name="refer_friends">Refer Friends</string>
    <string name="wallet_add_money">Proceed to add money</string>
    <string name="enter_wallet_money">₹   Enter Amount</string>
    <string name="proceed_add_money">Add money to</string>
    <string name="total_points">Total Points Earned</string>
    <string name="claim">Claim Reward</string>
    <string name="earn_amt">Earn Amount</string>
    <string name="earn_amt_line">Invite your friends to SkilEx and earn more money!</string>
    <string name="mobile_number_tag">: \n</string>
    <string name="user_name">Name</string>
    <string name="user_address">Door No/Building Name/Street Name</string>
    <string name="user_address1">Area/Locality</string>
    <string name="user_mail">E-Mail</string>
    <string name="user_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="select_user_gender">Select Gender</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="trend">Trending Services</string>
    <string name="trend_text">Take a look at some of the popular services from SkilEx!</string>

    <!--Google API key-->

    <string name="google_android_map_api_key">AIzaSyDyXHfwZjnPVy5reE5XPRZfmqMJd254hj4</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1654012428093090</string>
<!--    <string name="google_android_map_api_key">AIzaSyD428E0W4-pf4kJuJ3rsqG5vCELRgmR2ok</string>-->

    <!--Login-->

    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="skip_login">Skip for now</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="enter_text">Enter Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="login_to_continue">Log in to continue</string>

    <!--General-->

    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="progress_loading">Loading&#8230;</string>
    <string name="error_entry">Entry Invalid</string>
    <string name="error_mail">Enter vaild mail ID</string>
    <string name="error_number">Enter vaild phone number</string>
    <string name="empty_entry">Field cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="title_location_permission">Location Permission</string>
    <string name="text_location_permission">Allow app to access your location?</string>
    <string name="time">Select Time Slot</string>
    <string name="date">Select Date</string>
    <string name="time_selected">Requested Time Slot</string>
    <string name="date_selected">Selected Date</string>
    <string name="customer_name">Customer Name</string>
    <string name="cart">Cart</string>
    <string name="cart_clear">Items in cart will be cleared. Do you wish to continue?</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="choose_language">Choose your prefered language</string>

    <!--OTP Page-->

    <string name="verificationcode">Enter Verification Code</string>
    <string name="didntrecievecode">Didn\'t receive the code?\t</string>
    <string name="entercodetxt">We have sent a 4 digit verification code \n to your mobile number</string>
    <string name="resend">Resend now</string>
    <string name="resend_otp">Resend OTP?</string>
    <string name="changenumber">Change number</string>

    <!--Landing Page-->

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="services">Services</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="category_title">SkilEx Services</string>
    <string name="subcategory">Sub Category</string>
    <string name="search_result">Search Result</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>

    <!--Services Page-->

    <string name="req_services">Requested Services</string>
    <string name="ong_services">Ongoing Services</string>
    <string name="refer_and_earn">Refer and Earn</string>
    <string name="wallet_title">Skilex Wallet</string>
    <string name="use_wallet_amt">Use Wallet Amount</string>
    <string name="service_history">Service History</string>
    <string name="service_detail">Service Detail</string>
    <string name="service_cost">Cost after inspection. Minimum charge is</string>
    <string name="book_now">Book Now</string>
    <string name="inclusion">Inclusions</string>
    <string name="exclusion">Exclusion</string>
    <string name="procedure">Procedure</string>
    <string name="remove_service">Service Removed</string>
    <string name="others">Others</string>
    <string name="reason">Reason</string>
    <string name="comment">Comment</string>
    <string name="note">Notes (Optional)</string>
    <string name="cancel_service_alert">If you cancel you will not be refunded the advance amount paid. Are you sure you want to cancel?</string>
    <string name="cancel_service_noadvance_alert1">Are you sure you want to cancel your service?</string>

    <!--Ongoing Page-->
    <string name="about_service_person">About Service Expert</string>
    <string name="service_provider">Service Commando</string>
    <string name="service_starting_time">Service starting time</string>
    <string name="service_restarting_time">Service restarting time</string>
    <string name="service_restarting_date">Service restarting date</string>
    <string name="service_approximate">Estimated cost</string>
    <string name="cancel_service">Cancel Service</string>

    <!--Booking Page-->

    <string name="track">Tracking</string>
    <string name="booking">Booking summary</string>
    <string name="booking_status">Booking status</string>
    <string name="service_charge">Service charge</string>
    <string name="additional_charge">Additional charge</string>
    <string name="travel_allowance">Travel Allowance</string>
    <string name="additional_services">Addditional Services </string>
    <string name="grand_total">Total Service Cost</string>
    <string name="view_summary">View Summary</string>
    <string name="service_summary">Service Summary</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear All</string>

    <!--Payment Page-->

    <string name="access_code">Access Code</string>
    <string name="pay_button">Pay</string>
    <string name="pay_button_online">Pay Online</string>
    <string name="pay_button_cash">Pay by Cash</string>
    <string name="payment">Payment</string>
    <string name="merchant_id">Merchant Id</string>
    <string name="currency">Currency</string>
    <string name="amount">Amount</string>
<!--    <string name="redirect_url_advance">https://www.skilex.in/development/ccavenue_app/customer_advance.php</string>-->
<!--    <string name="redirect_url">https://www.skilex.in/development/ccavenue_app/service_net_amount.php</string>-->
    <string name="redirect_url_advance">https://www.skilex.in/ccavenue_app/customer_advance.php</string>
    <string name="redirect_url">https://www.skilex.in/ccavenue_app/service_net_amount.php</string>
    <string name="cancel_url">Cancel Url</string>
    <string name="rsa_url">RSA Key Url</string>
    <string name="advance_payment">Payment</string>
    <string name="advance_amount">Advance Amount</string>
    <string name="status">Payment Status</string>
    <string name="booking_success">Success!</string>
    <string name="booking_failed">Sorry!</string>
    <string name="booking_success_comment">Your booking completed \n successfully</string>
    <string name="booking_failed_comment">Your booking failed</string>
    <string name="wallet_success_comment">Money added to wallet \n successfully</string>
    <string name="wallet_failed_comment">Your transaction failed</string>
    <string name="payment_success">Awesome!</string>
    <string name="payment_failed">Something\'s wrong!</string>
    <string name="payment_success_comment">Your service order completed \n successfully</string>
    <string name="payment_failed_comment">Your service order failed</string>
    <string name="go_home">Back to Home </string>
    <string name="try_again">Try Again</string>
    <string name="failed">Failed</string>
    <string name="completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="view_bill">View Bill</string>


    <!--Profile Settings Page-->

    <string name="profile_title">Profile</string>
    <string name="about">About Skilex</string>
    <string name="share">Share app</string>
    <string name="rate_app">Rate app</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>


    <!--Rating Page-->
    <string name="rating_title">Rate Service</string>
    <string name="rating_text">Rate your service</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="rating">Reviews</string>

    <!--History Page-->
    <!--<string name="service_charge">Service Charge</string>-->
    <string name="sub_total">Sub Total</string>
    <string name="coupon_applied">Coupon Applied</string>
    <string name="coupon">Coupon</string>
    <string name="select_coupon">Select Coupon</string>
    <string name="apply_coupon">Apply</string>
    <string name="cancel_coupon">Cancel</string>
    <string name="grand_total_pay">Grand Total</string>
    <string name="service_person">Service Expert</string>
    <string name="share_invoice">Share Invoice</string>

    <!--About Us Page-->
    <string name="about_content">SkilEx is an emerging Indian start up that aims to build a scalable business model which serves as a platform connecting people, who are in need of local and personal services, with service Commandos. When there is need of service there is always a void in reaching to service experts at any given time. SkilEx comes into this scene of desperation to help consumers get the required service done at the right time. One can access a range of local services like refurbishment, renovation, restoration etc.; and personal services like fitness training, massages, physiotherapy, counselling, etc., via SkilEx and get things done in a convenient and affordable way.
\n\nInitially aimed at launching in major cities of South India, SkilEx’s vision is to expand its base across the country including all the cities, building a bond between the service Commandos and their customers.
</string>
<string name="terms_content">Terms of use

Skilex Multiservices Private Limited primarily operates, controls and manages the Services (as defined below) provided by it from its corporate office at 30/6, New Damu Nagar, Pappanaickenpalayam, Coimbatore-641037

Acceptance of Terms

PLEASE READ THE TERMS OF USE THOROUGHLY AND CAREFULLY. The terms and conditions set forth below ("Terms of Use") and the Privacy Policy (as defined below) constitute a legally-binding agreement between SkilEx and you. These Terms of Use contain provisions that define your limits, legal rights and obligations with respect to your use of and participation in (i)the SkilEx mobile application, all content and SkilEx services available through www.Skilex.in (collectively referred to herein as the "Application"), and (ii) the online transactions between those users of the mobile application who are offering services ("SkilEx Expert") and those users of the mobile Application who are obtaining services (“Customer") through the app. The Terms of Use described below incorporate the Privacy Policy and apply to all users of the app.

The SkilEx App is owned and operated by Skilex Multiservices Private Limited.

When you use any of the Services provided by us such as Electrical, Plumbing, Home cleaning Services, Carpentry etc., you will be subject to the rules, guidelines, policies, terms, and conditions applicable to such service, and they shall be deemed to be incorporated into this Terms of Use and shall be considered as part and parcel of these Terms of Use. As long as you comply with these Terms of Use, we grant you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited privilege to enter and use our platforms. In the event of a conflict or inconsistency between any provision of the terms and conditions mentioned herein with those of the particular service, the provisions of the terms and conditions applicable to such specific Services shall prevail.

These Terms of Use set forth legally binding terms for your use of our App. By using, visit, accessing our platforms, you agree to be bound by this Terms of Use, whether you are a “Guest” (which means that you simply browse our App) or you are a “Verified Customer” (which means that you have registered with SkilEx as a user). If you do not accept the Terms of Use, you should leave SkilEx App and discontinue use of the Service immediately.

We may modify these Terms from time to time, and such modification shall be effective upon its posting on our platforms. You agree to be bound by any modification to this Agreement when you use our SkilEx App after any such modification is posted; it is therefore important that you review the Terms of Use regularly.

Minors or people below 18 years old are not allowed to use this SkilEx App.

Registration Requirements

You also agree to provide true, accurate, complete information about yourself while registering on our SkilEx App to avail the Services, you should promptly update and maintain your Registered date to be true and accurate.

If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, incomplete, or we have reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, incomplete, we reserve the right to suspend or terminate your account and refuse any and all current or future use of our SkilEx App (or any portion thereof) at any time. SkilEx will not be liable for any act or omission arising from the inaccurate information provided by you to us.

You will be required to enter a valid phone number while registering on SkilEx App as a Verified Customer. By registering your phone number with us, you consent to be contacted by us via phone or SMS notifications, in case of anyservice updates. If we do so, you will be provided the option to "opt-out" of receiving future communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below. If you are registered with the DND National registry you may not receive any promotional messages from us.

User Information

1. SkilEx business model provides you with location based SkilEx Experts. To facilitate this, you hereby authorize SkilEx to use the location based information provided by any of the telecommunication companies when you use the mobile phone to make a booking. The location based information will be used only to facilitate and improve services for you.
2. If you use the App, you agree that information about your use of the SkilEx App through your mobile device may be communicated to us, and we may obtain information about your mobile device, or your location. By accessing the SKILEX App using a mobile device, you represent that to the extent you import any of your SkilEx data to your mobile device that you have authority to share the transferred data with other access provider. In the event you change or deactivate your mobile account, you must promptly update your SkilEx account information to ensure that your messages are not sent to the person that acquires your old number and failure to do so is your responsibility. You acknowledge that you are responsible for all charges and necessary permissions related to accessing the SKILEX App through your mobile. Therefore, you should check with your provider to find out if our SKILEX App are available and the terms for these services for your specific mobile devices.
3. SkilEx reserves the right to collect user data including name, contact information and other details to facilitate the Services or use of its SKILEX App to avail Services.
4. Compilation of user accounts and user accounts bearing contact number and e-mail addresses are owned by SkilEx.
5. In the case where the system is unable to establish unique identity of the user against a valid mobile number or e-mail address, the account shall be indefinitely suspended. SkilEx reserves the full discretion to suspend a user's account in the above event and does not have the liability to share any account information whatsoever.
6. We may record your calls to our call centers or to Us.

Termination or Suspension

You agree that SkilEx may at any time terminate your access to the SkilEx restrict or suspend your access to all or any part the App at any time, for any or no reason, with or without prior notice, and without liability.

Preservation/Disclosure

You acknowledge, consent and agree that SkilEx may access, preserve and disclose your account information and content if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

enforce these Terms of Use.
respond to your requests for customer service.
protect the rights, property or personal safety of SkilEx, its users and the public.
Security Components

You understand that SkilEx App and software embodied within the SkilEx App may include security components that permit digital materials to be protected, and that use of these materials is subject to usage rules set by SkilEx and/or content providers who provide content to SkilEx.

Usage of Services

1. If the service required by you necessitates the entry of SkilEx Expert into your premises, you must ensure the active supervision of the SkilEx Expert. SkilEx will be unable to provide services in the absence of any supervisors appointed by you at the service address.
2. If you have any questions or complaints regarding the services rendered, you may revert to us within the time specified for the category of services availed. Depending on the category of service availed, SkilEx will provide you with the appropriate recourse to address your concerns.
3. All invoices and payments due to SkilEx must be cleared immediately upon completion of the task or on the submission of the invoice, whichever is earlier.
4. You are requested not to solicit the services of the SkilEx Expert. SkilEx will not be responsible for any acts, service quality of the SkilEx Expert if You have engaged the services of such SkilEx Expert without reference to SkilEx.

What safeguards we have in place to protect your Personal Information?

All payments on the mobile app are secured. This means all Personal Information you provide is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us.

Indemnification

You hereby indemnify to the fullest extent SkilEx from and against any and/or all liabilities, costs, demands, causes of action, damages and expenses arising in any way related to your breach of any of the provisions of these terms.

Force Majeure

Without limiting the foregoing, under no circumstances shall SkilEx be held liable for any damage or loss due to deficiency in performance of the SkilEx Service resulting directly or indirectly from acts of nature, forces or causes beyond its reasonable control, including without limitation, Internet failures, computer equipment failures, telecommunication equipment failures, other equipment failures, electrical power failures.


If you have any complaint or grievance to report, please write to the Grievance Officer at info@skilex.in</string>

</resources>
